flex.com 2019-05-06

# | Flex

**PART A ABOUT FLEX'S USE OF PERSONAL DATA**

  1. **1   THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**

    1. **1.1   Our Privacy & Cookies Notice**

Flex takes its obligations to protect privacy and personal information very seriously. Please read this Privacy & Cookies Notice (" **the Notice** ") carefully as it sets out important information relating to how we handle your personal information.

  1. **1.2   Flex companies issuing the Notice**

In this Notice, references to "we", "us", "Flex" or "Flextronics" are references to Flex and all its group companies listed in Part B of this Notice. This Notice sets out how we, as data controller, will  collect and use personal information, and the choices and rights available to you in connection with our use of your personal information.

On occasion, the Flex group company who is the data controller in the EEA as set out in Part B of this Notice will be a joint controller with another Flex group company. Where the other Flex group company is based outside the EEA, then the data controller responsible for responding to requests to exercise data subject rights will be the relevant company in the EEA set out in Part B of this Notice. In all cases, any complaints and requests to exercise data subject rights should be addressed to the Data Privacy Liaison Officer and the Data Privacy Liaison Officer will arrange for the responsible joint controller to handle the complaint or request. 

  1. **1.3   To whose personal information does this Notice apply ?**

This Notice describes our practices when using:

a. the personal information of the business contacts, employees of clients  (including customers of our clients) of, and suppliers to, all our group companies 

b. set out in Part B of this Notice ("business contacts"); and other persons who (1) may visit our websites ("website users") or (2) who may visit our Flex pages on social media sites.

This Notice will apply whether you have provided the information directly to us or we have obtained it from a different source, such as a third party.

**2   BUSINESS CONTACTS**

**2.1   Sources of business contact information**

We collect personal information from our business contacts directly or from  the following sources:

• Third party referrals;

• Client checking and verification processes such as due diligence checks;

• Social media sites such as LinkedIn and other public internet sites;

• Credit reference agencies, insurance information bureaus and government or financial institutions; and

• Other public resources such as telephone directories, newspapers, internet sites, commercially available marketing lists, registries or public records.

**2.2   What personal information we collect about business contacts**

The categories of information we collect about business contacts includes:

• _Personal details including name, home address, employer, office address, personal and work telephone numbers and home and work email addresses;_

• _Financial details including payments made and received and VAT/sales tax;_

• _Goods or services provided or purchased_ ;

• Communications with our business contacts;

• Where business contacts have online accounts, log-in and similar credentials and information about use of these services;

• Image capturing, such as photos taken at events, videos, and CCTV footage;

• In certain circumstances criminal proceedings, outcomes and sentences, subject to applicable law.

**2.3   How we use the personal information we collect about business contacts**

We use this information for certain activities, including:

• Facilitating smooth running of the business through communication with corporate customers and suppliers, for example, to communicate about the goods and services we receive from suppliers;

• Maintaining and building upon customer and supplier relationships;

• Business planning;

• To fulfil a transaction initiated by a business contact;

• To fulfil a transaction initiated by a member of the Flex Group such as the purchase of supplies or equipment;

• To fulfil a transaction with, or for, Flex customers;

• Keeping accounts related to any business or other activity carried on by Flex;

• Deciding whether to accept any person as a customer or supplier;

• Keeping records of purchases, sales or other transactions for the purpose of ensuring that the required payments and/or deliveries are made or services provided;

• Completion of customer satisfaction surveys;

• Research and development;

• Business development;

• Event management  including inviting our business contacts to events and exhibitions;

• Database management;

• Running competitions;

• Security and crime prevention;

• For fraud and theft prevention or investigation, or other risk management purposes;

• Compliance with contractual, legal and regulatory obligations;

• Enabling business contacts to access their online accounts;

• For internal analysis and research to help us improve our services;

**2.4   Why we use the personal information of business contacts**

We use this information because:

• It is necessary for performing our obligations, or exercising our rights, under our contracts with customers or suppliers;

• It is necessary for compliance with any legal or regulatory obligations that we are subject to;

• We have a legitimate business interest to:

   •  Manage our business and brand;

   •  Provide and improve our services;

   •  Operate our business;

A legitimate interest will only apply where we consider that it is not outweighed by a business contact's interests or rights which require protection of their personal data.

• In limited circumstances, such as in the case of marketing, a business contact's consent as required under applicable law. Where we rely upon a business contact's consent, they will have the right to withdraw their consent by contacting the Data Privacy Liaison Officer.

If a business contact  requires further information regarding our legitimate interests as applied to their personal information, they may contact the Global Data Privacy Officer.

In certain circumstances, where a business contact does not provide personal information which is required, we will not be able to perform our obligations under the contract with them or may not be able to provide them with products and services. We will make it clear if and when this situation arises and what the consequences of not providing the information will be for the business contact.

  1. **2.5   Recipients of business contact information**

  2. We may disclose personal information of business contacts to third parties as follows:

• to Flex group companies in order to process the data for the above mentioned purposes;

• Business associates and other professional advisers;

• Third parties including for the purpose of event management;

• Claimants, beneficiaries, assignees and payees

• To suppliers and/or providers of goods and services and other third parties who work on our behalf to service or maintain business contact databases and other IT systems, such as suppliers of the IT systems which we use to process personal information, or who provide other technical services, such as printing;

• to third parties providing services to us, such as our professional advisors (e.g. auditors and lawyers);

• to competent authorities such as tax authorities, courts, regulators and security or police authorities where required or requested by law or where we consider it necessary; and

• subject to applicable law, in the event that Flex is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets (including in bankruptcy), or in the event of another corporate change, in connection with such transaction.

**2.6   Further Information**

Please see sections 4 to 8 below for further information concerning our use of personal data.

  1. **3   WEBSITE USERS AND WEB-RELATED PRIVACY ISSUES**

    1. **3.1   What personal information we collect about website users and visitors to Flex social media pages**

  2. The categories of information we collect about users of our website and Flex webpages on social media sites such as Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn and Twitter include:

• Information users provide when they enter information on our website, such as when they provide contact details, answer online questionnaires, feedback • • • forms or applications for employment or submit CVs

• Information provided when users subscribe to email newsletters such as name, email address, job title;

• Information users provide when registering for an online account through our website;

• Information users provide when posting content on social media sites.

We also collect personal information about the use of our website from users, including:

• Information captured in our web logs such as device information (e.g. device brand and model, screen dimensions), unique identification numbers (e.g. IP address and device ID), and browser information (e.g URL, browser type, pages visited, date/time of access);

• Advertising information (such as size/type of ad, ad impressions, location/format of ad, data about interactions with ad);

• Behavioural information (such as information on the behaviour or presumed interests of individuals which are linked to those individuals and may be used to create a user profile); and

• Information captured by our cookies (see **Cookies** section below).

If a website user does submit their data via one of our forms and they have cookies installed on their browser, all behavioural and web log data will be associated back to them. The website user will be informed of this when completing our forms.

Flex also uses cookie technologies (e.g. VWO) which fully anonymise your personal information (such as IP address or keystrokes) therefore the information cannot be traced back to a website user.

**3.2   How we use the personal information of website users and visitors to Flex social media pages:**

We use personal information of users of our website and Flex webpages on social media sites such as Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn and Twitter for certain activities, including:

• Personalizing the experience of our website;

• Providing products and services that website users have requested;

• Administering the website, investigating any complaints and providing customer services;

• Providing website users and individuals accessing our web pages on social media sites with information and offers on products or services that may be of interest to them;

• Monitoring social media content to manage relations with our customers and promote our business and brand.

• We use personal information about the use of our website for certain activities, including:

  •   Administering the website;

  •   Performing statistical and trend analysis to improve the user experience and performance of our website.

**3.3   Why we use the personal information of website users and visitors to Flex social media pages:**

We use personal information of users of our website and Flex webpages on social media sites such as Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn and Twitter because:

• It is necessary for compliance with any legal or regulatory obligations w we are subject to;

• We have a legitimate business interest to:

  •  Promote our brand and business through our website and through social media tools;

  •  Monitor, investigate and report any attempts to breach the security of our websites;

A legitimate interest will only apply where we consider that it is not outweighed by a website or social media user's interests or rights which require protection of their personal data; and

• In the case of marketing, a user's consent as required under applicable law. Where we rely upon a user's consent, they will have an option to "Unsubscribe" and will also have the right to withdraw their consent by contacting the Data Privacy Liaison Officer

We use personal information about the use of our website because:

• It is necessary for compliance with any legal or regulatory obligations that we are subject to;

• We have a legitimate business interest to:

• Monitor, investigate and report any attempts to breach the security of our websites;

• Improve the performance and user experience of our websites;

A legitimate interest will only apply where we consider that it is not outweighed by a website or social media user's interests or rights which require protection of their personal data.

If a website user or individual accessing our web pages on social media sites requires further information regarding our legitimate interests as applied to their personal information, they may contact the Global Data Privacy Officer.

In certain circumstances, where a website user does not provide personal information which is required (for example, in relation to our online services), we will not be able to perform our obligations under the contract with them or may not be able to provide them with products and services. We will make it clear if and when this situation arises and what the consequences of not providing the information will be for the website user.

  1. **3.4   Recipients of personal information of website users and visitors to Flex social media pages**

We may disclose website and social media users' personal information to third party recipients, as follows:

• to Flex group companies in order to process the data for the above mentioned purposes;

• to third parties who work on our behalf to service or maintain Software as a Service platforms for our websites such as SFDC or Pardot, other suppliers of • • • the IT systems which we use to process personal information, or third parties who provide other technical services, such as printing;

• to third parties providing services to us, such as our professional advisors (e.g. auditors and lawyers);

• to competent authorities such as tax authorities, courts, regulators and security or police authorities where required or requested by law or where we consider it necessary;

• subject to applicable law, in the event that Flex is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets (including in bankruptcy), or in the event of another corporate change, in connection with such transaction.

  1. **3.5   Further Information**

Our websites and online services are for individuals who are at least 18 years of age. Our online services are not designed to be used by children under the age of 18.

Please see sections 4 to 8 below for further information concerning our use of personal data.

  1. **4.   INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

Flex is a global company and, as such, we may transfer personal information to other Flex group companies or suppliers outside your home jurisdiction. Flex will take all reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is protected and any such transfers comply with applicable law.

Flex may transfer and maintain the personal information of individuals covered by this Notice on servers or databases outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Some of these countries may not have the equivalent level of protection under their data protection laws as in the EEA.

The countries to which we transfer data outside of the EEA include:  Brazil, Canada, China, Hong Kong, India, Indonesia, Israel, Japan, Malaysia, Mauritius, Mexico, Philippines, Russia, Switzerland, Singapore, South Korea, Taiwan, Turkey, Ukraine and the USA.

If we need to transfer personal data outside the EEA, we will take steps to make sure your personal data is protected and safeguarded once it leaves the EEA, in particular:

  1. 1.  the use of Binding Corporate Rules under Article 47 of the GDPR.

  2. 2.  the use of Model Clauses approved by the European Commission and permitted under Article 46 of the GDPR.

If you would like to obtain the details of such safeguards, you can request these from the [Global Data Privacy Officer].

Our Data Privacy Standards including information on your third party beneficiary rights, are available on our website at [www.flex.com](http://www.flex.com/)

  1. **5   RETENTION PERIODS**

We will retain your personal information for as long as required to perform the purposes for which the data was collected, depending on the legal basis for which that data was obtained and/or whether additional legal/regulatory obligations mandate that we retain your personal information.  We may also retain personal information for the period during which a claim may be made in relation to our dealings with you.  

In general terms, this will mean that your personal data will be kept for the duration of our relationship with you and:

  1. 1.  the period required by tax and company laws and regulations; and

2.  as long as it is necessary for you to be able to bring a claim against us and for us to be able to defend ourselves against any legal claims. This will generally be the length of the relationship plus the length of any applicable statutory limitation period under local laws

In certain circumstances, data may need to be retained for a longer period of time, for example, where we are in ongoing correspondence or there is a continuing claim or investigation.

If you wish to obtain further information about the retention periods as applied to your personal information, you may find this in the retention schedule maintained by Flex or can contact the Global Data Privacy Officer.

  1. **6   DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS**

Individuals have the following rights, in certain circumstances, in relation to their personal information:

  1. 1.  Right to access personal information.

  2. 2.  Right to rectify personal information.

  3. 3.  Right to restrict the use of  personal information.

  4. 4.  Right to request that  personal information is erased.

  5. 5.  Right to object to processing of  personal information.

  6. 6.  Right to data portability (in certain specific circumstances).

  7. 7.  Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

A summary of each right and how an individual can take steps to exercise it is set out below and in our Global Data Subject Rights Policy which is available on our website .

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the contact details specified

below for the Data Protection Liaison Officer. Such requests should include appropriate identity verification information (such as your name, address, email address or other information reasonably required).

Where we receive a request to exercise one of these rights, we shall provide information on the action we take on the request without undue delay and in any event within one month of receipt of the request. This may be extended by a further two months in certain circumstances, for example where requests are complex or numerous.

The information will be provided free of charge, except where requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive, in particular because of their repetitive character. In these circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee or may refuse to act on the request. We will advise an individual  of any fees prior to proceeding with a request.

We may ask for additional information to verify an individual's  identity before carrying out a request.

Where we do not carry out a request, we shall inform the individual without delay and within one month of receipt of the request, providing our reasons for not taking the action requested.

**Right to access personal data**

Individuals have the right to confirm the following with us:

  1. 1.  Whether or not we process personal data about them

  2. 2.  Certain specified information about the processing

Individuals also have a right to access the personal data and be provided with a copy.

**Right to restrict processing of personal data**

Individuals have the right to request that we restrict processing of their  personal data where one of the following applies:

  1. 1.  An individual contests the accuracy of the personal data. The restriction will apply until we have taken steps to verify the accuracy of the personal data;

  2. 2.  The processing is unlawful but an individual  does not want the personal data to be erased and  requests restriction instead;

  3. 3.  We no longer require the personal data for the purposes of processing, but it is still required by an individual  in connection with a legal claim;

  4. 4.  An individual has exercised their right to object to the processing. The restriction will apply until we have taken steps to verify whether we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing.

  5.   6. **Right to object to processing of personal data**

  7. Where  personal data is used to target marketing to an individual , they have the right to object to this at any stage.

An individual  also has the right to object to processing of their  personal data where the legal basis of the processing is our legitimate interests. We will have to stop processing until we are able to verify that we have compelling legitimate grounds for processing which override the individual's interests, rights and freedoms, or alternatively that we need to continue processing for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

  8. **Right to rectification of personal data**

  9. If an individual  believes that the personal data we hold on them is inaccurate, they may request that it be amended. They may also request that incomplete personal data be completed, including by providing a supplementary statement.
  10.  
  11. **Right to request erasure of personal data ("right to be forgotten")**

  12. An individual may also request the erasure of their personal data in certain circumstances, including the following (this is not an exhaustive list):
  13. 1.  The personal data is no longer necessary in relation  to the purposes for which 

  14. 2.  they were collected or otherwise processed;

  15. 3.  The processing was based on consent which has been  withdrawn  and there is no other legal basis for processing;

  16. There are also certain exceptions where we may refuse a request for erasure, for example, where the personal data is required to comply with a legal obligation or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

  17. If an individual does request erasure of their personal data, this will potentially remove records which we hold for their benefit, such as their presence on a suppression list and they will have to contact us to provide personal information if they wish for us to hold this in future.

  18.   19. **Right to Data Portability**

  20. Where we are relying upon the legal basis either of consent or that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which an individual  is  a party, and that personal data is processed by automatic means (e.g. electronically), an individual  has the right to receive all the personal data which they have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit this to another controller directly, where this is technically feasible.
  21.  
  22. **Supervisory Authority**

  23. An individual also has a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State in the European Union where they are habitually resident, where they work or where an alleged infringement of data protection laws has taken place.
  24. **7   MISCELLANEOUS**

    1. **7.1   Security**
  25. We have put in place technical and organisational security measures to prevent the loss or unauthorised access of your personal information. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. However, whilst we have used our best efforts to ensure the security of your data, please be aware that we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted over the Internet. If you have reasons to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us as set out below.

  26.   27. **7.2   Links**

  28. Our Website may contain links to other "non-Flex" websites. We do not control and assume no responsibility for the content, security or the privacy policies and practices on those websites.

Flex encourages all users to read the privacy policies of those sites to determine how they protect and use personal information.

  29.   30. **7.3   Changes to this Notice**

  31. From time to time, we may change and/or update this Notice. If this Notice changes in any way, we will post an updated version on this website. We recommend you regularly review this website to ensure that you are always aware of our information practices and any changes to such. Any changes to this Notice will go into effect on posting to this page.

  32.   33. **8   COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**

  34.   35. A cookie is a small text file which includes a unique identifier that is sent by a web server to the browser on your computer, mobile phone or any other internet enabled device when you visit an on-line site. Cookies and similar technologies are widely used to make websites work efficiently and to collect information about your online preferences.  For simplicity, we refer to all these technologies as "cookies".

Some of our website pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons (also known as clear gifs, tags or pixels) that allow us to count users who have visited our pages. Web beacons collect only limited information, e.g. a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any information that could directly identify you.

  36.   37. **8.1   How do we use cookies?**

  38.   39. We use cookies and other tracking technologies to customise content and advertising, provide social media features and to see how our visitors move through our website. We use this information to make decisions about ways to improve the services we offer you.

We may engage third party tracking and advertising providers such as those named below to act on our behalf to track and analyse your usage of our website through the use of cookies. These third parties collect, and share with us, usage information about visits to our website and, sometimes by correlating this information with other information (e.g. your IP address), measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, track page usage, help us target our recommendations and advertising, and track use of our recommendations and advertisements.

  40.   41. **8.2   Cookies and types of cookies what we use**

  42.   43. The table below describes the cookies that we use.

  44. **Cookie name / provider / type**

| 

**What these cookies do**  
  
---|---  
  
Google Analytics

__utma

__utmb

__utmc

__utmz

| 

These cookies enable the function of Google Analytics. This software allows us to measure and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, visitor numbers, and which pages are used. We use this information to help improve our Website.

investors.flex.com  
  
Google Analytics _ga

| 

The analytics.js library uses a single cookie named _ga to store a unique client identifier (Client ID), which is a randomly generated number. This ID is used by Google Analytics servers to calculate

visitor, session, and campaign data. We use this information to help improve our Website. [www.flex.com](http://www.flex.com/)  
  
Act-on

| 

Act-On uses cookies to collect information about the use of this site. The Act-On Cookie tracks movement through all the sections of Flex's site that are beaconed for marketing information and persists until browser policy time or cache clear. The session cookie gathers the information about the IP address to attach a unique identifier for the user, it does not collect any other personal identification. Although Act-On plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Act-On. Act-On’s ability to use and share information collected by Act-On about your visits to this site is restricted by the Act-On Terms of Use and the Act-On Privacy Policy. You can prevent Act-On from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.   
  
Pardot

| 

Pardot (Salesforce) uses three types of cookies to track website visitor activities. Cookies are used to remember preferences and to track clickpath for when a visitor returns to the site to build a profile in order to target marketing which is relevant for the user. The three types of cookies are:

    * A visitor cookie composed of a unique visitor ID and unique identifier for Flex's account.

    * The pi_opt_in cookie tracks opt-in preferences and is set with a true or false value when the visitor opts in or out of tracking.

    * A session cookie named "pardot" is set when someone is logged in as a Pardot user. This is not set up on a website visitor's browser.   
  
Sumo

**__smShown**

__smListBuilderShown

__smSmartBarShown

__smScrollBoxShown

__smWelcomeMatShown

__smSubscribed

__smUser

__smToken

__smDashView

| 

__smShown

The cookie is set when any of the List Builder, Welcome Mat, Scroll Box or Smart Bars are shown on your website. If you have any of your Popups/Mats set to "Don't Show to a visitor until X days have passed", and Sumo detects this cookie in the visitors browser, it will not show that certain Popup/Mat.

This cookie is unique to the email apps and will display in your browser cookie list like this:

The **__smSubscribed**  cookie is set when a visitor subscribes via any of the List Builder, Welcome Mat, Scroll Box or Smart Bars they are shown on your website. If you have any of your Popups/Mats set to "Not Show To Users Who Already Subscribed", and Sumo detects this cookie in the visitors browser, it will not show that certain Popup/Mat.

The **__smUser** cookie is set when you login to Sumo on your website and the cookie value is your User ID

The **__smToken** is set once you login to Sumo and is checked to verify whether you are logged into Sumo or not.

The **__smDashView** cookie restores the same tab you were last in when you go back into the "Dashboard" app. For example, if you close the Dashboard app while in the "Subscriber Stats" tab, the next time you open the app, the cookie will allow the app to be opened in the exact tab you were last in.  
  
VWO (anonymised)

_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_goal_GOAL_ID:

_vis_opt_test_cookie

_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_combi

_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_exclude

_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_split

_vis_opt_s

_vis_opt_out

_vwo_uuid

_vis_opt_exp_EXPERIMENT_ID_

| 

This cookie is generated when a goal is created.

This is a temporary session cookie generated to detect if the cookies are enabled on the user browser or not.

This cookie is generated when users reach a particular combination. This cookie ensures that users see the same variation that they saw on their previous visit to the page.

This cookie is generated when a user is excluded from a test.

This cookie is generated during a Split URL test.

This cookie detects if the user is new or returning to a particular test.

This cookie indicates that the visitor is not part of the test. This cookie is valid for 10 years.

EXPERIMENT ID refers to the ID of the test, and GOAL ID refers to the ID of the goal.

This cookie generates a unique ID for every visitor and is used for the report segmentation feature in VWO. It also allows you to view data in a more refined manner. If you have a test running on multiple domains, you will notice test-specific UUID values.

In the combi cookie, the Control always has the value of 1, Variation #1 always has the value of 2, Variation #2 has the value of 3, and so on.  
  
Other targeting cookies

| 

We may use other cookies to target and re-target visitors to our websites with digital advertising that is most relevant to the user.  These cookies are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert or particular content, as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising or marketing campaign. Using existing cookies from many sites already on your computer, we partner with 3rd party companies to deliver advertising to specific computers. For more information about digital advertising visit AdChoices at: [www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/).  
  
Social media cookies

| 

These cookies allow users to share our websites on social media such as Facebook and Twitter. These cookies are not within our control. Please refer to the respective privacy policies of the social media provider for how their cookies work.  
  
Performance cookies

| 

These cookies collect information on how users use our websites, in order to help us improve areas such as navigation, and to help us fix technical issues or errors. For example, we use these cookies to help us understand how you arrive at our website, browse or use our website and highlight areas where we can improve our website.  
  
Functionality cookies

| 

These cookies help us customise our website content based on a user's preferences. They remember the user's choices such as identifying the user as a particular investor type (Retail, Professional or Institutional), their language, the country pages visited and any changes the user makes to text size or other parts of our website pages. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track browsing activity on other websites.  
  
Essential cookies

| 

These cookies are essential for parts of our website to operate. They enable users to move around our website and allow us to recognise a user within our website so that we can provide them with service they asked for such as remembering the user's sign-in details.  

You can find more information about cookies, behavioural advertising and online privacy at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [www.youronlinechoices.eu.](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) 

**10.4   How do I reject cookies?**

If you do not want to be tracked by Google Analytics cookies you can opt-out by installing a browser plug-in here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

At any time, you can prevent cookies from being set on your browser. For instructions on how to block, delete or disable any cookies, please consult your browser's 'Help' or 'Support' section. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our website.

Please consult the following links for information on cookie management and blocking according to your browser:

Explorer: [http://windows.microsoft.com/en-gb/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11.](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-gb/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11)

Firefox: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)

Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)

Safari: [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=en_GB](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?locale=en_GB)

Pardot uses a persistent cookie named "pi_opt_in" to stay in compliance with the "Do Not Track" initiative and allow for opt out of types of browser tracking. Pardot’s tracking code can optionally respect these headers and does not use cookie-based tracking for any visitors with this setting enabled.

You can also find more information and manage cookie storage at: [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

**FLEX RECRUITMENT NOTICE**

**PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA**

Flex International USA, Inc. of 6201 America Center, San Jose, CA, USA, and all other Flex group companies (hereafter Flex) takes its obligations to protect privacy and personal information very seriously.

**Contact details:** Your personal information is collected by Flex Int ("we"/"us"/"our"). You can contact us at [hrcompliance@flex.com](mailto:hrcompliance@flex.com). If you have any questions or complaints in relation to the use of your personal information or this Recruitment Notice, you can contact our Data Privacy Officer at: [chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com](mailto:chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com)

**Personal Information Collected:** We collect, the information below about you during the recruitment process. If you fail to provide certain information when requested, we will not be able to progress your application.

  * Information provided in your curriculum vitae, application form, covering letter and during the interview process including: your name, date of birth, age, gender, home address, personal email address, education, qualification and work experience details, and references.
  * Information collected or created by us during the recruitment process including: interview notes, test scores and correspondence between us.
  * Information about criminal convictions: we carry out background checks as part of the recruitment process.

Special categories of personal data including: Racial and ethnic origin information [and information relating to disabilities, religious beliefs or sexual orientation], physical or mental health information and immigration/naturalisation records (if this discloses racial/ethnic origin information).

**Sources of Information:** This information is either (a) provided by you; (b) obtained from third parties through the application and recruitment process; (c) obtained from public sources, such as LinkedIn, or (d) created by us in the course of the recruitment process.

**How we use personal information:** We use your personal information to progress the recruitment process, assess and make a decision about your suitability for a role, to communicate with you and to carry out reference checks. We will also use your information to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

**Why we use personal information:** We will use the information collected from you because:

  * it is necessary for us to do so before entering into a contract with you;
  * we need to process your information in order to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation;
  * because we or a third party have a legitimate interest to: (a) ensure the effective administration and management of the recruitment process; (b) ensure we hire a suitable individual for a role; (c) deal with disputes and accidents and take legal or other professional advice; and (d) ascertain your fitness to work.

**How we use special category personal information:** We will process your special categories of personal data to consider whether we need to provide appropriate adjustments for any disabilities during the recruitment process; (2) for equal monitoring purposes; (3) comply with any legal or regulatory obligation.

**Why we use special category personal information:** We will use special categories of personal information collected about you because: (1) you have provided your explicit written consent;(2) we need to do so to carry out our legal obligations; (3) it is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence or legal claims on in relation to court cases; [(4) there is a substantial public interest;] (5) it is needed to protect your interests (or someone else's interests) and you are not capable of giving your consent.

**Information about criminal convictions:** As part of the recruitment process we carry out criminal background checks. We use these checks (1) to assess your suitability for a regulated role; (2) to protect your interests, our interests and third party interests; (3) because it is necessary in relation to legal claims. We are allowed to use your personal information in this way where it is necessary to carry out our employment rights and obligations and we will always process your data in accordance with applicable local law.

**Automated decision making:** Following a [background check/ psychometric test] an automated decision will be reached on whether to progress your application or offer you employment based on whether yours satisfy our benchmark criteria. If you disagree with the decision you are entitled to contest this by contacting us at following email address: [chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com](mailto:chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com)

**Information that we share:** We will only share your personal information with the following third parties for the purposes of processing your application: (1) employment agencies, (2) background check and online test providers, and (3) regulators and competent authorities. We will also share personal data within our group for the purposes of administration, accounting and reporting purposes.

**Retention of your information:** We will retain your personal information for the duration of the recruitment process and for the length of any applicable limitation period for claims which might be brought against us later.

**Where your information will be held:** We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to other flex entities outside the EU for the purposes of management and administration of the recruitment process subject to us implementing appropriate safeguards. If you would like to obtain copies of such safeguards you can request them from us on the contact details above.

**Your rights:** You have the following rights in connection to your data: the rights of access, correction, erasure, objection, restriction, transfer, and the right to withdraw consent and to complain to a Supervisory Authority.

**Note :** While this global policy is designed to deliver consistent and efficient information to candidates on global basis , all information will always be processed in accordance with applicable local law

**PART B FLEX GROUP COMPANIES AND HOW TO CONTACT US**

Flex and all its group companies listed below will have access to information on individuals covered by this Notice .

**How to Contact Us**

Our Global Data Privacy Officer is the Data Protection Officer for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be

addressed to our Global Business Services ( **GBS** ) team or our Global Data Privacy Officer through

the following means:

**GBS:**

Email Address: [dataprivacy@flex.com](mailto:dataprivacy@flex.com)

**Global Data Privacy Officer:**

Email Address: [chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com](mailto:chiefprivacyofficer@flex.com)

**Name of Subsidiary**

| 

**Jurisdiction**

| 

**Registered Address**

| 

**Contact point (if relevant)**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Flextronics International Gesellschaft m.b.H.

| 

Austria

| 

Friesacher Strasse 3, 9330 Althofen, Austria

|   
  
Masa da Amazônia Ltda.

| 

Brazil

| 

com sede na Cidade de Manaus, Estado da Amazonas, na Avenida Solimões nº 805, Distrito Industrial, CEP: 69075-200, inscrita no CNPJ/MF sob o nº 04.454.120/0001-10

|   
  
Flextronics International Tecnologia Ltda

| 

Brazil

| 

com sede na Cidade de Sorocaba, Estado de São Paulo, na Avenida Liberdade, nº 6.315, Prédios 09,10,11 e 12 Bairro Iporanga CEP: 18087-170, inscrita no CNPJ/MF sob o nº 74.404.229/0001-28, Brazil

|   
  
Flextronics Global Services Canada Inc.

Services Globaux Flextronics Canada Inc.

| 

Canada

| 

77 King Street West, Toronto-Dominion Centre Suite, Toronto, Ontario M5K 0A1, Toronto, ON, M5K 0A1, Canada

|   
  
Flextronics Canada Design Services Inc.

| 

Canada

| 

333 Bay St, Suite 2900, 333 Bay Street, Suite 2900, Toronto, ON, M5H 2T4, Canada

|   
  
Flextronics Information Technology (Shen Zhen) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

Room 801/901, North Building, Resources-Tec-Building, NO.1, Songpingshan Road, North Beihuan Avenue, Shenzhen High-Tech Industrial Park, Nan Shan District, Shenzhen, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics (China) Electronics Technology Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

Room 122, Huaxia Technology Building. Building No.8,Zhongguancun Software , Haidian District, Beijing, the People’s Republic of China, 100094, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics (Shanghai) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

Room 301, Block C, No.177, Bibo Road, Zhangjiang Hi-Tech Park, Shanghai., China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Power Systems Technologies (Beijing) Company Limited

| 

China

| 

Room 405, 4th Floor, 2nd Block, B Building, No. 12, Hong Da North Road, Beijing Eco-Tech Development Area, Beijing, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Power Systems (Dongguan) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

Flextronics DongGuan Industrial Park,Shi Da Road ,Da Ling Shan ,Dongguan, Guangdong, China, 523817, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics R&D (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

2/F, Block 8, Vision Shenzhen Business Park,GaoXin Ave. 9th S., Hi-tech Industrial Park, NanShan District, ShenZhen, 518057, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Chengdu Flextronics Mechanical Manufacturing Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

Industry Concentration Development Area, Economic Development Zone of Southwest Air Harbor, ShuangLiu Town, Chengdu City, Sichuan Province

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Plastics (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

1F, 2F, 7F Building 1, & 2F Building 2,Yusheng Industrial Park,467 Xixiang Section, National Highway 107, Xixiang, Baoan District,Shenzhen, Guangdong, China, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Global Enclosures (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

No.15 Plant,GFM13-10,Waigaoqiao Free Trade Zone, Shanghai, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Plastic Technology (ShenZhen) Ltd.

| 

China

| 

Ji Xiang Industrial Park, Huang Tian Village,Xi Xiang,Bao An,Shenzhen, P.R.China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Enclosure (Zhuhai) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

(BeiJing Room, 1ST Floor) Block A, No.1 Xin Tang Road, Jin An Town, DouMen, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek Electronics Limited

| 

China

| 

Room223, 2nd Floor, Plant B2，No.2 Xin Tang Road, Xin Qing Science & Technology Industrial Park, Jin An Town, Doumen, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek Industries Limited

| 

China

| 

Plant B3、B12，No.2 Xin Tang Road, Xin Qing Science & Technology Industrial Park, Jin An Town, Doumen, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek Zhuhai Limited

| 

China

| 

Block 1, No.2Haiyedong Road,San Zao Town, Jin Wan District, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek China Limited

| 

China

| 

No.2021 Zhu Feng Avenue, Xin Qing Science & Technology Industrial Park, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek Technology (Zhuhai) Co Limited

| 

China

| 

Rm224, 2nd floor Plant B2，No.2 Xin Tang Road, Xin Qing Science & Technology Industrial Park, Jin An Town, Doumen, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Industrial (Shenzhen) Co Ltd

| 

China

| 

1F\3-7F Building 2 & Building 3, Yusheng Industrial Park,467 Xixiang Section, National Highway 107, Xixiang,Baoan District,Guangdong, Shenzhen

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Technology (ShenZhen) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

Building 1,Yusheng Industrial Park,467 Xixiang Section, National Highway 107,xixiang,Baoan District,Guangdong., Shenzhen

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Technology (Nanjing) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

No.99 Zhuang Pai Road, Jiang Ning Development Zone,Nanjing, Jiangsu 211100, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Electronics Technology (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

1F-4F 1ST Blk E and 1F blkA, Jiehe Industrial Zone Shuitian community Shiyan street, Baoan district, Shenzhen, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Automotive (Suzhou) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

Unit 2, standard factory of Morern Industrial Fang, Suzhou Industrial Park,Suzhou, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Electronics Technology (Suzhou) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

No#9 Suqian road, Suzhou industrial Park,Suzhou, JiangSu , China 215021, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Computing (Suzhou) Co., Ltd

| 

China

| 

No.1 Guanpu Road,Guoxiang Street, Wuzhong, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Technology (Zhuhai) Co. Ltd.

| 

China

| 

Shanghai Room, 1ST Floor) No.1 Pu Qing Street, Jin An Town, DouMen, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Industrial (Zhuhai) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

NO. 168, Zhufeng Rd., XinQing Science & Technology Industrial Park, Jing An Town, Doumen, Zhuhai, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing (Zhuhai) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

No.38,XinWei Street,Jin An Town,Dou Men, Zhuhai

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Technology (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

No. 77 Yongsheng Road, Malu, Jiading, Shanghai 201100 China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Dongguan Flextronics Precision Metal Co., Ltd.

| 

China

| 

988 Room, Block 9 No 263, Hong Da Road Qiaotou Town, Dongguan, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing (Tianjin) Co., Ltd. 

| 

China

| 

2F, No.10,Forth Avenue ,Tianjin Economic-Technological Development Area

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek (FTZ) Limited

| 

China

| 

Free trade Zone, ZhuHai City, China

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Design, s.r.o.

| 

Czech Republic

| 

Řípská 1464/11D, Slatina, Brno, 627 00, Czech Republic

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Sønderborg Værktøjsfabrik A/S

| 

Denmark

| 

Elholm 6, 6400, Sonderborg, Denmark

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Denmark A/S

| 

Denmark

| 

Flextronics International Denmark A/S, c/o BDO Statsaut. revisionsaktieselkab, Slotsgade 3, Skive, 7800, Denmark

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International s.r.o.

| 

Czech Republic

| 

Starocernska 226, Cerna za Bory, Pardubice, Czech Republic

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Holding Finland Oy

| 

Finland

| 

Regus Kone Building, Keilasatama 3, ESPOO, 02150, Finland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Laval S.N.C.

| 

France

| 

2 rue Pégase, Aéroparc 1, ENTZHEIM, 67960, France

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Automotive GmbH & Co. KG

| 

Germany

| 

Arthur B, Modine - Strabe 1, Filderstadt, 70794, Germany

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Power Systems Technologies GmbH

| 

Germany

| 

Arthur B, Modine - Strabe 1, Filderstadt, 70794, Germany

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Multilayer Technology GmbH & Co. KG

| 

Germany

| 

Arthur B, Modine - Strabe 1, Filderstadt, 70794, Germany

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
 Power Systems Technologies Far East Limited

| 

Hong Kong

| 

17/F, Nina Tower (Tower II), 8 Yeung Uk Road, Tsuen Wan, New Territories, Hong Kong, Hongkong

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
 Flextronics Manufacturing (H.K.) Limited

| 

Hong Kong

| 

17/F, Nina Tower (Tower II), 8 Yeung Uk Road, Tsuen Wan, New Territories, Hong Kong, Hongkong

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Multek Hong Kong Limited

| 

Hong Kong

| 

17/F, Nina Tower (Tower II),8 Yeung Uk Road, Tsuen Wan, New Territories, Hong Kong, SAR, Hong Kong

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Kft.

| 

Hungary

| 

8660 Tab, Munkas Str.28, H-8660, Hungary

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Technologies (India) Private Limited

| 

India

| 

Plot No. 3, Phase II, SIPCOT Industrial Park, Sriperumbudur Taluk, Kancheepuram Dist. Tamil Nadu, Sandavellure C Village, India, 602106, India

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
PT. Flextronics Technology Indonesia

| 

Indonesia

| 

Jalan Rambutan Lot 515,Muka Kuning, Batam City 29433, Indonesia, Indonesia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Irish Express Cargo Limited

| 

Ireland

| 

Unit 10 Keypoint, Rosemount Business Park, Ballycoolin Road, Blanchardstown, Dublin, 11, Ireland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Cork B.V. (Irish)

| 

Ireland

| 

Kilbarry Industrial Estate, Dublin Hill, Cork, Ireland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics (Israel) Ltd.

| 

Israel

| 

1 Hatahasia St. P.O.X 867, Ramat Gavriel Ind. Zone, Migdal Haemek, 23108, Israel

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Design S.r.l.

| 

Italy

| 

Milan via Ernesto Breda 176 -20126 Milano

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Italy S.p.A.

| 

Italy

| 

Via Strada Statale, 234, 1/3, Somaglia, LO, 26867, Italy

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics S.R.L.

| 

Italy

| 

Ponte Di Piave (TV), Via A. Dalla Torre, 6/A, Levada, 31047, Italy

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Japan Co., Ltd.

| 

Japan

| 

367-2, Sekidate, Chikusei-shi, Ibaraki, 308-0193, Japan

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Design Korea Ltd.

| 

Korea

| 

#501, Daemyoung global biz square, 1746-3, Gwanyang-dong, Dongan-gu, Gyeonggi-do, Anyang-si, Korea

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Marketing (L) Ltd.

| 

Labuan

| 

Level 1, Lot 7, Block F, Saguking Commercial Building., Jalan Patau-Patau, Federal Territory of Labuan, 87000, Malaysia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Technology (Penang) Sdn. Bhd.

| 

Malaysia

| 

Unit 30-01, Level 30, Tower A, Vertical Business Suite, Avenue 3, Bangsar South, No. 8, Jalan Kerinchi, 59200 Kuala Lumpur, 59200, Malaysia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Technology (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd.

| 

Malaysia

| 

Plot D26, Jalan DPB/4, Kawasan Zon Perindustrian Bebas,Pelabuhan Tanjung Pelepas, 81560 Gelang Patah, Johor, Malaysia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Shah Alam Sdn. Bhd.

| 

Malaysia

| 

Unit 30-01, Level 30, Tower A, Vertical Business Suite, Avenue 3, Bangsar South, No. 8, Jalan Kerinchi, 59200 Kuala Lumpur, 59200, Malaysia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Technology (Shah Alam) Sdn. Bhd.

| 

Malaysia

| 

Unit 30-01, Level 30, Tower A, Vertical Business Suite, Avenue 3, Bangsar South, No. 8, Jalan Kerinchi, 59200 Kuala Lumpur, 59200, Malaysia

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Industrial Ltd.

| 

Mauritius

| 

Level 3, Alexander House,35 Cybercity, Ebene,Mauritius, Mauritius

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics International Asia-Pacific Ltd 

| 

Mauritius

| 

Level 3, Alexander House,35 Cybercity, Ebene,Mauritius, Mauritius

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing Mex, S.A. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Carretera Base Aerea # 5850-4, Fracc. La Mora, C.P, Zapopan, Jalisco, 45136, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Plastics, S.A. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Corporation Trust Center, 1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE 19801, Wilmington, DE, 19801

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing Aguascalientes, S.A. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Carretera a la Base Aerea No. 5850-4 Col La Mora, CP, Zapopan, Jalisco, 45136, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Technologies Mexico, S. de R.L. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Carretera a la Base Aerea No. 5850-4 Col La Mora, CP, Zapopan, Jalisco, 45136, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Availmed, S.A. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Carretera Base Aerea No. 5850 Int. 4 Colonia La Mora, Zapopan, Jalisco, Mexico 45136, 45136, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing Juarez, S. de R.L. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Carretera Base Aerea # 5850-4, Fracc. La Mora, C.P, Zapopan, Jalisco, 45136, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Automotive de Juarez, S.A. de C.V.

| 

Mexico

| 

Calle Omega No. 1825, Parque Industrial Omega, Juarez, Chihuahua. 32410, Chihuahua, 32410, Mexico

| 

Karelli Solorio <[karelli.solorio@flex.com](mailto:karelli.solorio@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Logistics B.V.

| 

Netherlands

| 

Nobelstraat 10-14, 5807 GA Oostrum Lb, The Netherlands, Netherlands, Europe

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
ThermoMend B.V.

| 

Netherlands

| 

Nobelstraat 10 t/m 14, 5807GA Oostrum

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Logistics Poland Sp. z o.o.

| 

Poland

| 

Al. Ofiar Terroryzmu 11 Wrzesnia 17, 92-410 Lodz, Poland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Poland Sp. z o.o.

| 

Poland

| 

Ul.Malinowska 28, 83-100 TCZEW, Poland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Automotive USA Design and Development Corporation

| 

Philippines

| 

Sinulog Drive, Mactan Economic Processing Zone II, Lapu-Lapu City, Cebu 6015 Philippines

| 

James Liu(SHZ) [james.liu3@flex.com](mailto:james.liu3@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics România SRL

| 

Romania

| 

Timisoara, Calea Torontalului DN 6, KM 5, 7, Timis, RO, 300668, Romania

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Design Asia Pte. Ltd.

| 

Singapore

| 

2 Changi South Lane, Singapore 486123, Singapore

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Plastics (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.

| 

Singapore

| 

No. 2 Changi South Lane , Singapore 486123, Singapore, 486123

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Power Systems R&D (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.

| 

Singapore

| 

2 Changi South Lane, JIT Logistic Centre, 486123, Singapore

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Manufacturing (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.

| 

Singapore

| 

2 Changi South Lane, 486123, Singapore

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics International Sweden AB

| 

Sweden

| 

Box 25 372 21 Ronneby

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flex Precision Plastics Solutions (Switzerland) AG

| 

Switzerland

| 

Sonnhalde, 5607 Hägglingen, Switzerland

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics International Taiwan Ltd.

| 

Taiwan

| 

5F, No.6, Sec. 1, Jhongsing Rd.,Wugo Township, Taipei County, 248 Taiwan, R.O.C., Taiwan

| 

Danarajah Al Sivapragasam <[danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com](mailto:danarajah.sivapragasam@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Global Services Lojistik Hizmetleri Limited

Şirketi

| 

Turkey

| 

Karamehmet Mahallesi Avrupa Serbest Bolgesi Avrasya Bulvari No:31 Ergene/Tekirdag, Turkey

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
FLEXTRONICS INTERNATIONAL LOJİSTİK HİZMETLER TİCARET LİMİTED ŞİRKETİ

| 

Turkey

| 

Karamehmet Mahallesi Avrupa Serbest Bolgesi Avrasya Bulvari No:31 Ergene/Tekirdag, Turkey

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Express Cargo Forwarding Limited

| 

UK

| 

Stretton Green Distribution Centre, Langford Way, Warrington, Cheshire, WA4 4TQ

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics Global Services (Manchester) Limited

| 

UK

| 

STRETTON GREEN DISTRIBUTION CENTRE LANGFORD WAY,WARRINGTON,CHESHIRE,WA4 4TQ.

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
 Public Joint Stock Company “Flextronics Service UA”

| 

Ukraine

| 

4, Berehivska - bіchna St., 89600 Mukacheve, Zakarpatska Oblast, Ukraine, Ukraine

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Commercial Company in the form of a limited liability

company factory “Flextronics LLC”

| 

Ukraine

| 

4, Berehivska - bіchna St., 89600 Mukacheve, Zakarpatska Oblast, Ukraine, Ukraine

| 

Ferdinand Trauttenberg [Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com](mailto:Ferdinand.Trauttenberg@flex.com)  
  
Flextronics America, LLC

| 

USA

| 

1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE, 19801, U.S.A.

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Lighting Solutions, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

Corporation Trust Center, 1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE 19801, Wilmington, DE, 19801

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Logistics USA, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

818, West Seventh Street, 2nd Floor, Los Angeles, CA, 90017, United States

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Multek Flexible Circuits, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

Corporation Trust Center, 1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE 19801, Wilmington, DE, 19801

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Pacific Device, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

CT Corporation, 1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE, 19801, U.S.A.

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Elementum SCM, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

818 West 7th Street, Los Angeles, CA 90017, 90017

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Automotive USA, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

2120 Austin Avenue, Rochester Hills, MI 48309

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Automotive USA Manufacturing Co.

| 

USA

| 

30600, Telegraph Road, Bingham Farms, MI, 48025, United States

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics International USA, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

818 West 7th Street, Los Angeles, CA 90017, 90017

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Advance Mold & Manufacturing, Inc. 

| 

USA

| 

One Corporate Center, Floor 11, Hartford, CT 06103-3220

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Automotive USA (Texas), LLC

| 

USA

| 

811 Dallas Avenue, Houston, TX 77002

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>  
  
Flextronics Precision Plastics, Inc.

| 

USA

| 

Corporation Trust Center, 1209 Orange Street, Wilmington, DE 19801, Wilmington, DE, 19801

| 

Claudia Alvarez <[claudia.alvarez@flex.com](mailto:claudia.alvarez@flex.com)>
